<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Generated by crowdin.com-->
<resources>
    <string name="app_description">NetGuard provides simple and advanced ways to block access to the internet - no root required. Apps and addresses can individually be allowed or denied access to your Wi-Fi and/or mobile connection.</string>
    <string name="app_android">NetGuard requires Android 5.1 or later</string>
    <string name="app_privacy"><a href="https://www.netguard.me/privacy/">Privacy policy</a></string>
    <string name="app_first">Great care has been taken to develop and test NetGuard, however it is impossible to guarantee NetGuard will work correctly on every device.</string>
    <string name="app_agree">Ik ga akkoord</string>
    <string name="app_disagree">Ik ga niet akkoord</string>
    <string name="channel_foreground">Running services</string>
    <string name="channel_notify">General notifications</string>
    <string name="channel_access">Access notifications</string>
    <string name="msg_sure">Weet u het zeker?</string>
    <string name="msg_started">Regels worden toegepast</string>
    <string name="msg_packages">%1$d toegestaan, %2$d geblokkeerd</string>
    <string name="msg_hosts">%1$d toegestaan, %2$d geblokkeerd, %3$d hosts</string>
    <string name="msg_waiting">Wachten op gebeurtenis</string>
    <string name="msg_revoked">NetGuard is uitgezet, waarschijnlijk door een andere VPN applicatie</string>
    <string name="msg_installed">\'%1$s\' geïnstalleerd</string>
    <string name="msg_installed_n">Is geïnstalleerd</string>
    <string name="msg_access">%1$s benaderde het internet</string>
    <string name="msg_access_n">Probeerde verbinding te maken met het internet</string>
    <string name="msg_completed">Actie uitgevoerd</string>
    <string name="msg_vpn">NetGuard maakt gebruik van een lokale VPN om internetverkeer te filteren.
Vanwege deze reden vragen wij u de VPN-verbinding in het volgende dialoogvenster toe te staan.
Uw internetverkeer wordt niet verzonden naar een VPN-server.</string>
    <string name="msg_autostart">NetGuard kon niet automatisch worden gestart tijdens het opstarten vanwege een bug in uw Android-versie</string>
    <string name="msg_error">Er is een onverwachte fout opgetreden: \'%s\'</string>
    <string name="msg_start_failed">Android refused to start the VPN service at this moment. This is likely because of a bug in your Android version.</string>
    <string name="msg_dimming">Als u niet op \'Oké\' kan drukken in het volgende dialoogvenster, is een (schermdimmende) app waarschijnlijk actief.</string>
    <string name="msg_kbsec">%7.3f KB/s</string>
    <string name="msg_mbsec">%7.3f MB/s</string>
    <string name="msg_doze">For consistent results, the Android battery optimizations should be disabled for NetGuard.
\n\nIn the next dialog, select \"All apps\" at the top, tap on NetGuard in the list and select and confirm \"Don\'t optimize\".</string>
    <string name="msg_datasaving">For consistent results, the Android data saving options should be disabled for NetGuard
\n\nIn the next dialog, enable the options \"Background data\" and \"Unrestricted data usage\"</string>
    <string name="msg_update">Update beschikbaar, tik om te downloaden</string>
    <string name="msg_issue">Please describe the problem and indicate the time of the problem:</string>
    <string name="msg_vpn_cancelled">VPN connection cancelled\nDid you configure another VPN to be an always-on VPN?</string>
    <string name="msg_on">Powering down your device with NetGuard enabled, will automatically start NetGuard on powering up your device</string>
    <string name="msg_always_on">Another VPN is set as Always-on VPN</string>
    <string name="msg_always_on_lockdown">Turn off \"Block connections without VPN\" in Android VPN settings to use NetGuard in filtering mode</string>
    <string name="msg_private_dns">Turn off \"Private DNS\" in Android network settings to use NetGuard in filtering mode</string>
    <string name="title_internet">heeft geen internet toegang</string>
    <string name="title_allow_wifi">Allow Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="title_block_wifi">Block Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="title_allow_other">Allow mobile</string>
    <string name="title_block_other">Block mobile</string>
    <string name="title_root">root</string>
    <string name="title_mediaserver">mediaserver</string>
    <string name="title_nobody">niemand</string>
    <string name="title_dontask">Niet opnieuw vragen</string>
</resources>
