<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Generated by crowdin.com-->
<resources>
    <string name="app_description">AMon supports the investigation project MDSM developed by NESG.
        \n\nAMon will gather non-sensitive information from your device to mobile devices security.
        \n\nAll the information will be sent to a remote server for future study.</string>
    <string name="app_android">AMon requires Android 6.0 or later</string>
    <string name="app_first">AMon will gather non-sensitive data from your device to support the investigation project MDSM.  More information related to the gathered data and its functionality can be found in this <a href="https://nesg.ugr.es/mdsm/downloads/detallesAMon.pdf">link</a>.   AMon will be running in background after its activation and won\'t disturb the user experience.
        \n\nIn order to continue you must accept the <a href="https://nesg.ugr.es/mdsm/downloads/TerminosUso.pdf">Terms of use</a></string>
    <string name="app_agree">I agree</string>
    <string name="app_disagree">I disagree</string>
    <string name="channel_foreground">Running services</string>
    <string name="channel_notify">General notifications</string>
    <string name="channel_access">Access notifications</string>
    <string name="msg_sure">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="msg_started">Enforcing rules</string>
    <string name="msg_packages">%1$d allowed, %2$d blocked</string>
    <string name="msg_hosts">%1$d allowed, %2$d blocked, %3$d hosts</string>
    <string name="msg_waiting">Waiting for event</string>
    <string name="msg_revoked">AMon has been disabled, likely by using another VPN based app</string>
    <string name="msg_installed">\'%1$s\' installed</string>
    <string name="msg_installed_n">Has been installed</string>
    <string name="msg_access">%1$s attempted internet access</string>
    <string name="msg_access_n">Attempted internet access</string>
    <string name="msg_completed">Action completed</string>
    <string name="msg_vpn">AMon uses a local VPN to register internet traffic. For this reason, please allow a VPN connection in the next dialog.</string>
    <string name="msg_autostart">AMon could not start automatically. This is likely because of a bug in your Android version.</string>
    <string name="msg_error">An unexpected error has occurred: \'%s\'</string>
    <string name="msg_start_failed">Android refused to start the VPN service at this moment. This is likely because of a bug in your Android version.</string>
    <string name="msg_dimming">If you cannot press OK in the next dialog, another (screen dimming) app is likely manipulating the screen.</string>
    <string name="msg_doze">For consistent results, the Android battery optimizations should be disabled for AMon.
\n\nIn the next dialog, select \"All apps\" at the top, tap on AMon in the list and select and confirm \"Don\'t optimize\".</string>
    <string name="msg_datasaving">For consistent results, the Android data saving options should be disabled for AMon
\n\nIn the next dialog, enable the options \"Background data\" and \"Unrestricted data usage\"</string>
    <string name="msg_issue">Please describe the problem and indicate the time of the problem:</string>
    <string name="msg_vpn_cancelled">VPN connection cancelled\nDid you configure another VPN to be an always-on VPN?</string>
    <string name="msg_on">Powering down your device with AMon enabled, will automatically start AMon on powering up your device</string>
    <string name="msg_always_on">Another VPN is set as Always-on VPN</string>
    <string name="msg_always_on_lockdown">Turn off \"Block connections without VPN\" in Android VPN settings to use AMon in filtering mode</string>
    <string name="msg_private_dns">Turn off \"Private DNS\" in Android network settings to use AMon in filtering mode</string>
    <string name="title_internet">has no internet permission</string>
    <string name="title_dontask">Don\'t ask again</string>
    <string name="textSwitchOn">AMon enabled</string>
    <string name="textSwitchOff">AMon disabled</string>
    <string name="battery_saving">Battery Saving</string>
    <string name="go">Go</string>
    <string name="step">Step %1$d</string>
    <string name="step_description_batterySaving">Select \"Battery Saving\" and choose \"No restrictions\"</string>
    <string name="step_description_autostart">Check \"Autostart\"</string>
    <string name="step_description_lock">Open the Recent screen (also known as Recent Apps or Recent Task List). Then, lock AMon swiping or long pressing on it and pressing the lock icon. (This last step can vary between Android versions)</string>
    <string name="step_doze">Allow AMon to ignore battery optimizations.</string>
    <string name="step_data">Enable \"Background data\".</string>
    <string name="amon_help">To switch AMon state, click on the logo.</string>
    <string name="step_no">All the battery saving changes have been done.</string>
    <string name="msg_working">AMon is running in the background.</string>
    <string name="msg_blocked">Some application has been blocked.</string>
    <string name="msg_connection_lost">Internet connection is unavailable.</string>
    <string name="app_battery">Disabling battery optimization is needed for AMon to perform correctly.
\n\nFollow the proposed steps in the next screen to disable battery optimization.
\n\nThis menu can be accessed later by the menu shown in the main screen.</string>
    <string name="about_amon">About AMon</string>
    <string name="channel_update">Update notifications</string>
    <string name="update_msg">A new version is available</string>
    <string name="step_still"><b>Note:</b> Since the application cannot check all the changes made, some steps may have been done and still be shown here.</string>
    <string name="step_description_more">Optimization according to the manufacturer.</string>
</resources>
